danscomp.com 2019-06-14

# Privacy Policy

##  Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information 

Thank you for visiting DANSCOMP.COM. This notice explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. OUR ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES MAY DIFFER FROM OUR PRACTICES REGARDING INFORMATION OBTAINED OFFLINE. 

REMEMBER IF YOU REGISTER WITH DANSCOMP.COM, PARTICIPATE IN A SURVEY, PURCHASE SOMETHING FROM US, REQUEST A CATALOG OR ENTER ANY OF OUR CONTESTS OR PROMOTIONS, YOU AGREE TO THESE TERMS. AS WE UPDATE AND EXPAND OUR SERVICES, THIS POLICY MIGHT CHANGE, SO CHECK IT OUT FROM TIME TO TIME.

The security of your information is important to us. We have implemented reasonable administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the unauthorized access, destruction or alteration of your information based on its sensitivity. Despite our best efforts, however, no security measures are completely impenetrable.

**The Information We Collect.**  
At DANSCOMP.COM you can do a variety of things! You may be able to order products, enter contests, participate in surveys, vote in polls, subscribe to a service (like our ezine) or participate in a chat room. The types of personally identifiable information (i.e. information that can directly identify you or indicate where you might be contacted) that may be collected at these pages includes: name, address, date of birth, sex, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. You can view or change your information at any time by sending an email to[ customerservice@danscomp.com](mailto:customerservice@danscomp.com)

Sometimes you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to a friend, you might submit the friend's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient's name, address, age, date of birth, grade level, e-mail address, sex and telephone number.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e. generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer or Google Chrome), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows 10 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Comcast or Time Warner).

**How We Use and Disclose Your Personal Information.**  
We will use the personal information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of us using your personal information for the purpose(s) submitted include if you order a catalog, we will send to you a catalog in the mail or if you have won a contest, sending to you an email notification that you have won. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services which we think you may be interested in or to ask you to participate in a survey. For example, we may send to you an e-mail regarding special merchandise offers and announcements about products or services offered by Dan's Comp. We may also contact you offline. For example, when you provide your mailing address, Dan's Comp may send to you in the mail special offers, promotions and catalogs, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please contact us at[ customerservice@danscomp.com](mailto:customerservice@danscomp.com)

**How We Share Your Personal Information.**  
We will not share the personal information you provide except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it; (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another); (d) with other persons or companies with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the site); and/or (e) notifying you when we make changes to one of our subscriber agreements or this policy.

Examples of us sharing your personal information for the purposes submitted are if you request information regarding financial aid, we may provide the information provided to a third party lender so that they can send to you directly the information you requested or, if you enter a contest or sweepstakes sponsored by a third party, we may forward your information to that third party. Additionally, with your consent, we may share certain of the personal information you provide online with companies not affiliated with us (i.e. third party companies) who are interested in marketing their products or services to you or in asking you questions, both online and offline. Such companies may include consumer products, telecom, financial, military, market research, entertainment, and educational services companies and their third party service providers. If you want us to stop sharing your personal information with these companies, please contact us at[customerservice@danscomp.com ](mailto:customerservice@danscomp.com)If you consent to receiving communications from non-affiliated companies, you may need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications or if you wish to change any data you provided online. In this instance, any changes or amendments to your personal information must be given directly to each company who communicates with you as these changes, amendments and/or deletions will not be exchanged between us and non-affiliated companies.

We will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an "opt-in" or "opt-out" method, or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail).

If we do share personal information to a non-affiliated company, to the extent practical, we require that they protect such information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. We cannot, however, guarantee how these non-affiliated companies will use your personal information.

**Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information.  **  
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze how our site is used, as well as to offer you products, programs or services. Sometimes we share aggregate information with others, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies.

**Collection of Information by Others.**  
Our site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should check the other sites' privacy notices since we have no control over information that is submitted to or collected by them.

We may offer e-mail services, contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with non-affiliated companies. Based on our agreement with them, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that site visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. We have no control over the use of this information by these companies.

**Cookies.**  
To enhance your online experience with us, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files placed on your hard disk by our web server to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, once you choose to provide the personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies as a convenience feature to save you time, to understand how our site is used, and to improve the content and offerings on our site. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages or recall your specific information on subsequent visits (e.g. to recognize you by name when you return to our site). We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services. You can opt to have your browser reject cookies. If you do that, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our site in order to participate in certain promotions and other stuff. You should also know that companies that advertise on our web site (and their agents) might use their own cookies. This policy does not cover how these companies use their cookies.

**International Compliance** (GDRP)

We may store your information in the United States and in other locations outside of the European Economic Area. Any transfer of your data to the United States or another location outside the European Economic Area will be in compliance with applicable European data protection laws and in respect of transfers to the United States comply with the E.U. – U.S. and Swiss – U.S. 

If you are located outside the United States and provide personal data to us through doing business, your personal data is being collected on servers located in the United States. The data is collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy and normal course of business. Dan's Comp does not retain credit card information. General address information is retained for mailing and shipping purposes. 

Our Obligations to you under GDRP: Dan's Comp complies with the E.U. – U.S. and Swiss – U.S. GDRP Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce and approved by the European Commission and Swiss Federal Council regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information Dan's Comp receives from European Union member countries and Switzerland.

Dan's Comp adheres to the Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access and Recourse. Enforcement and Liability in respect of any personal data received from International customers. We collect and process data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the GDRP Principles, GDRP princeples shall govern. 

Dan's Comp is required to take certain steps when transferring personal information received from the European Union and Switzerland to third parties (such as including necessary contractual provisions in our third party contracts). Dan's Comp may be potentially liable in cases of onward transfer of EU and Swiss individuals' data received pursuant to GDRP and third parties. Privacy Complaints Handling, Recourse and Enforcement  
In compliance with GDRP Principles, Dan's Comp commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information (without charge to you). European Union and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact us at: - privacy@DanComp.com We will respond to any complaints as soon as possible; normally within 4-5 days.

We encourage International customers who have questions or complaints about how we process their Personal Data under GDRP to contact us at privacy@DanComp.com. We will work to resolve your issue as quickly within 4-5 days of receipt of complaint as possible. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use complaint that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please call toll free 888-888-3267. If you are an EU or Swiss individual and unable to resolve any complaints through any of the above methods, you may be able to invoke binding arbitration through a Privacy Shield panel, in accordance with the Privacy Shield Framework at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>. Dan's Comp is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission in the case of any failure to comply with the Privacy Shield. 

**How You Can Access or Correct Your Personal Information.**  
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that we have collected about you online, or how to correct any errors in such information, you may call 888-888-3267 and select option 3 for Customer Service or send an e-mail to [customerservice@danscomp.com](mailto:customerservice@danscomp.com). If you have a online user account, you may also log into your account and update the information. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**Special Note for Parents.**  
If you have concerns about this site or its services, wish to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our services, or wish to cancel your child's membership, please contact us at [customerservice@danscomp.com ](mailto:customerservice@danscomp.com). Our site will not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under 13 years old in violation of applicable laws. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to our site without your permission, you may contact us at [customerservice@danscomp.com ](mailto:customerservice@danscomp.com). We have taken commercially reasonable steps to restrict use of this site to those who are at least 13 years old. We do not knowingly sell products for purchase by children and all children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only, or with adult permission.

**Transfer of Business Assets.  **  
The personal information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among transferred assets if Dan's Comp, any or all of its subsidiaries or affiliates or any of their assets is acquired by a third party.

**Changes to this Policy.  **Because our business needs may change over time, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use your personally identifiable information in a way that differs from this policy, we will revise this policy as appropriate. Your continued use of our DANSCOMP.COM following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. This policy is effective as of April 24, 2018 **.**

**How to Contact Us.**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may e-mail [privacy@danscomp.com](mailto:privacy@danscomp.com) or write to the following address:

Dan’s Competition  
C/O XP Innovation, LLC  
1 Competition Way  
Mt. Vernon, IN 47620  
Attn: Privacy  
812-838-2850
